They took my battle ostrich!
- Oh, no, not Glenn!
- Yes!
(Sheldon:)Glenn!
(Sheldon:)The only bird I ever loved.
(Policeman:)Good luck, fellas.
Oh. Well, thank you, officer.
(Sheldon:)Wait a minute!
(Sheldon:)You're not going to do anything?
(Policeman:)Mr. Cooper,
there's nothing...
(Policeman:)Dr. Cooper.
(Policeman:)Seriously?
(Leonard:)Not the kind with
access to drugs.
(Policeman:)Fine. Dr. Cooper.
(Policeman:)I'm sorry for your loss,
(Policeman:)but the Pasadena
Police Department
(Policeman:)doesn't have
jurisdiction in...
(Policeman:)Pandora.
That's from Avatar!
(Leonard:)World of Warcraft
takes place in Azeroth.
(Sheldon:)Goodness gracious, how are you
allowed to carry a gun?
(Sheldon:)Can you at least refer me
to a rogue ex-cop?
(Policeman:)What?
Wh-- you know, one who was
drummed off the force
(Sheldon:)because he refused
to play by the rules,
(Sheldon:)and now he hires himself out
(Sheldon:)to impose his own brand
of rough justice?